http://www.wgasc.org/privacy-policy-terms-of-use/

Skip to main content Skip to primary sidebar
MenuHomeAboutWGASC HistoryCorporate PartnersHonorsMediaBlogContact Us CloseCalendarColor Guard EventsPercussion/IPA Events CloseEnsembles/EventsGuardsSchedules, Scores, and Show Information – GuardNews – WGASC News / InformationGuard Ensemble RosterGuard Ensemble ProfilesNew Ensemble RegistrationRegistering My EnsembleClassifieds – Classified sales and announcementsGuard Score ArchivesScholarship Info ClosePercussion/IPASchedules, Scores, and Show Info – Percussion/IPANewsPercussion/IPA Ensembles RosterPercussion/IPA Ensemble ProfileNew Ensemble RegistrationPercussion Score ArchivesClassifieds – Classified sales and announcements Close CloseResources2021 Solo CompetitionScholarship ApplicationWGASC/ADLA/IPA New Ensemble RegistrationWGASC Virtual Series Close
Search
Search
CloseADLA RSSWGASC RSS CloseADLA facebookWGASC facebook Close
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience – your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
To improve our website – we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To improve customer service – your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit card details, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all registered members of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Member Information’ page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy / Terms of Use.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
Credit Card Charges and Order Fulfillment
Credit Card charges for orders placed on the site are submitted immediately and automatically finalized on a daily basis. Fulfillment items (tickets, etc) are sent within 7 days from receipt of order – unless the order is submitted and processed too close to an event date, in which case the tickets will be available for pickup (with proper identification) at the venue.
Refunds
Refunds will be handled at the discretion of the WGASC Executive Board.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy / Terms of Use,  you may contact us using the methods below.
Mail
Winter Guard Association of Southern California
16027 Brookhurst Street, Suite G
PMB #334
Fountain Valley, CA 92708-1551
Phone
714.839.3025
Contact Form
http://www.wgasc.org/about/contact-us
This page was last updated on: April 25, 2014
Primary SidebarSearch
Search this website
Most Recent News
Calling all Soloists and Small Ensembles! 2021 Season Update Design Possibilities for 2021 Webinar Registration for the 2021 season is OPEN! Indoor Performing Arts (IPA) Info. Meeting....TONIGHT!
